{"data":[{"question":"I like a nice cup of tea in the morning.' '________'","a":"So did I","b":"Nor did I","c":"Nor do I","d":"So do I","answer":"4","explain":"\n- To agree with a positive statement: so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I like running.' '_________'","a":"So do I","b":"So am I","c":"Neither do I","d":"So can I","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To agree with a positive statement: so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I didn't pass my driving test.' '_________'","a":"So did I","b":"Nor did I","c":"Neither did I","d":"Nor I did","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun\n\n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She is not married.' '________'","a":"Neither do I","b":"Neither can I","c":"Neither am I","d":"So am I","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun\n\n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She came yesterday'. '________'","a":"Neither did I","b":"So did I","c":"So am I","d":"So do I","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- To agree with a positive statement:  so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun\n\n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"We have never been to Germany.' _________","a":"So have they","b":"Nor have they","c":"Nor did they","d":"So did they","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"He didn't pass his driving test.' '________'","a":"So did I","b":"Nor do I","c":"Neither did I","d":"Nor I did","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She says she needs a holiday.' '_________'","a":"So did I","b":"So do I","c":"Nor do I","d":"Neither did I","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To agree with a positive statement: so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I've never been there.' '_________'","a":"So have I","b":"Neither have I","c":"Neither did I","d":"Neither do I","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun\n\n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I couldn't do it alone.' '_________'","a":"Nor could I","b":"Nor did I","c":"Neither did I","d":"So did I","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun\n\n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}